<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.bibeltv" name="Bibel.TV" version="3.0.3+matrix.1" provider-name="realvito">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
		<import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.27.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
		<provides>video</provides>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="de_DE">Der christlich ausgerichtete Free-TV-Sender</summary>
		<summary lang="en_GB">The Christian-oriented free-TV channel</summary>
		<description lang="de_DE">Bibel.TV ist ein deutschsprachiger Fernsehsender. Spielfilme, Dokus, Shows und viel Musik erwarten Sie - rund um die Uhr, 7 Tage in der Woche.[CR]Die Verbreitung des christlichen Glaubens steht im Mittelpunkt des Fernsehprogramms von Bibel.TV, das das gesamte Spektrum journalistischer und unterhaltender Sendeformate abbildet.</description>
		<description lang="en_GB">Bibel.TV is a German-language television channel. Movies, documentaries, shows and lots of music await you - around the clock, 7 days a week.[CR]Spreading the Christian faith is the focus of the television programme of Bibel.TV, which covers the entire spectrum of journalistic and entertaining broadcasting formats.</description>
		<disclaimer lang="de_DE">Die von diesem Addon dargestellten Inhalte werden von den Erstellern des Addons weder gehostet oder verbreitet, noch stehen die Ersteller in irgendeiner Beziehung zu den Anbietern des Inhalts.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_GB">The content displayed by this Addon is not hosted or distributed by the creators of the Addon, nor do the creators have any affiliation with the providers of the content.</disclaimer>
		<language></language>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 3, June 2007</license>
		<forum>https://www.kodinerds.net/thread/55451-l0res-blog-realvitos-fixing-thread/</forum>
		<website>https://www.bibeltv.de/home</website>
		<email></email>
		<mainsource>https://github.com/Collabsvito/REpo-AiO/</mainsource>
		<source>https://github.com/Collabsvito/REpo-AiO/tree/master/MATRIX/plugin.video.bibeltv</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>resources/media/icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>resources/media/fanart.jpg</fanart>
		</assets>
		<news>
[B][COLOR orangered]Version 3.0.3+matrix.1  (30.03.2025)[/COLOR][/B]
- fixed: LIVESTREAMS von Hope-TV, EWTN und K-TV (OpenInputStream - error opening)
- optimized: Neue Playerparameter für MPD-Streams in KODI-Omega/Piers
		</news>
	</extension>
</addon>
