<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.spotitube" name="You(T) Musicbox" version="3.0.8+matrix.1" provider-name="realvito (inspired by L0RE)">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
		<import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.27.0"/>
		<import addon="plugin.video.youtube" version="6.8.1+matrix.1"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
		<provides>video</provides>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="de_DE">Chartplayer für Musikvideos</summary>
		<summary lang="en_GB">Chartplayer for Musicvideos</summary>
		<description lang="de_DE">Musiktitel aus verschiedenen Quellen und Charts z.B. Beatport, Billboard, Officialcharts, Shazam etc. auswählen und das entsprechende Video automatisch auf YouTube suchen und über das YouTube-Addon abspielen.[CR][CR]     TEST IT AND LIKE IT</description>
		<description lang="en_GB">Select music titles from various sources and charts e.g. Beatport, Billboard, Officialcharts, Shazam etc. and automatically search for the corresponding video on YouTube and play it via the YouTube-Addon.[CR][CR]     TEST IT AND LIKE IT</description>
		<disclaimer lang="de_DE">Die von diesem Addon dargestellten Inhalte werden von den Erstellern des Addons weder gehostet oder verbreitet, noch stehen die Ersteller in irgendeiner Beziehung zu den Anbietern des Inhalts.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_GB">The content displayed by this Addon is not hosted or distributed by the creators of the Addon, nor do the creators have any affiliation with the providers of the content.</disclaimer>
		<language></language>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 3, June 2007</license>
		<forum>https://www.kodinerds.net/thread/55451-l0res-blog-realvitos-fixing-thread/</forum>
		<website></website>
		<email></email>
		<mainsource>https://github.com/Collabsvito/REpo-AiO/</mainsource>
		<source>https://github.com/Collabsvito/REpo-AiO/tree/master/MATRIX/plugin.video.spotitube</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>resources/media/icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>resources/media/fanart.jpg</fanart>
		</assets>
		<news>
[B][COLOR orangered]Version 3.0.8+matrix.1  (22.06.2025)[/COLOR][/B]
- fixed: 'OfficialCharts UK' sometimes the artist is not found and an error occurs
- added: Category = AppleMusic with some lists to choose from
- removed: Category = iTunes (Api switched off)
- removed: Category = Spotify (The Public-Categories of the Api are no longer freely available)
- optimized: Removed dependency and cache of webpages with 'script.common.plugin.cache'
- comment: * Due to various changes to the 'settings', these are automatically reset when the Addon is started for the first time and the YouTube-API-KEY must be entered again ! *
		</news>
	</extension>
</addon>
