<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.sportdeutschland_tv" name="Sportdeutschland.TV [COLOR FF00EE00](light)[/COLOR]" version="2.0.9+matrix.1" provider-name="realvito">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
		<import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.22.0+matrix.1"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
		<provides>video</provides>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="de_DE">Amateursport - Wettbewerbe</summary>
		<summary lang="en_GB">Amateur Sports - Competitions</summary>
		<description lang="de_DE">Sportdeutschland.TV ist der vom Deutschen Olympischen Sportbund (DOSB) im Jahr 2014 gegründete Online-Sportsender. Dem User stehen auf der Plattform über ca. 5.000 Stunden On – demand – Videos zur Auswahl.[CR]Zudem gibt es verschiedene Livestreams zu vielen Sportarten wie Handball, Basketball, Eishockey und Volleyball auf Sportdeutschland.TV.[CR][CR][COLOR FF00EE00]Dieses Addon stellt nur den FREI verfügbaren Inhalt von 'sportdeutschland.tv' zur Verfügung ![/COLOR]</description>
		<description lang="en_GB">Sportdeutschland.TV is the online sports channel founded by the German Olympic Sports Confederation (DOSB) in year 2014. The user can choose from over approx. 5.000 hours of On – demand – Videos on the platform.[CR]In addition, there are various live streams for many sports such as handball, basketball, ice hockey and volleyball on Sportdeutschland.TV.[CR][COLOR FF00EE00]This Addon only provides the FREE available content of 'sportdeutschland.tv' ![/COLOR]</description>
		<disclaimer lang="de_DE">Die von diesem Addon dargestellten Inhalte werden von den Erstellern des Addons weder gehostet oder verbreitet, noch stehen die Ersteller in irgendeiner Beziehung zu den Anbietern des Inhalts.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_GB">The author does not host or distribute any of the content displayed by this addon. The author does not have any affiliation with the content providers.</disclaimer>
		<language></language>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 3, June 2007</license>
		<forum>https://www.kodinerds.net/index.php/Thread/55451-L0REs-Blog/</forum>
		<website>https://sportdeutschland.tv/</website>
		<email></email>
		<mainsource>https://github.com/Collabsvito/REpo-AiO/</mainsource>
		<source>https://github.com/Collabsvito/REpo-AiO/tree/master/MATRIX/plugin.video.sportdeutschland_tv</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>resources/media/icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>resources/media/fanart.jpg</fanart>
		</assets>
		<news>
[B][COLOR orangered]Version 2.0.9+matrix.1  (06.08.2022)[/COLOR][/B]
- fixed: Es werden KEINE Bilder zu den Videos angezeigt (API verändert)
		</news>
	</extension>
</addon>
